frontiertouring.com 2018-01-31

# Privacy Policy | Frontier Touring Australia & New Zealand

**Table of Contents**

  1. Overview
  2. Collection of personal information
  3. Disclosure
  4. Quality of personal information
  5. Storage and security of personal information
  6. Accessing and correcting your personal information
  7. Unsubscribe
  8. How to make a complaint
  9. How to contact us
  10. Policy Changes

##  1.    Overview

Frontier Touring Co Music Pty Ltd (ACN: 005 602 602) (“Frontier, we, us, our”) respects the privacy of the individuals it deals with, and is committed to complying with its obligations under the Australian Privacy Principles (APP) which are contained in the Privacy Act (Cth) 1998.

This privacy policy outlines the personal information handling practices of Frontier.  It describes the types of personal information Frontier collects and explains how it holds, uses and discloses that information. This policy also explains how you can gain access to the personal information Frontier holds about you.

By using the website and submitting your personal information to us, you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information by us as set out in this Online Privacy Policy.

##  2.    Collection of personal information

We are an Australian and New Zealand promoter of music and entertainment goods and services. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, these are referred to as “our goods” and/or “services”.

Frontier collects personal information about you when you use the Frontier website http://www.frontiertouring.com and associated social media sites and ‘Apps’ (the “Sites”). We only collect information which is necessary for us to provide our goods and services to you.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

At all times we try to only collect the information we need for the particular function or activity we are carrying out. The main way we collect personal information about you is when you give it to us.

We may collect both anonymous information and personal information through the Sites.

Anonymous information is information that does not identify you. It includes

a.    analytics information – this is information that we log regarding access and use of the Website, including details of any computer used to access the Website (such as IP address, host and browser type), the date and time of access and details of webpages accessed and information downloaded; and

b.    profile information, if any – this is information that you provide for your online profile, including your music preferences, entertainment preferences  and region.

Personal information is information that could identify you. The personal information we hold may include, for example, your name, contact details such as telephone number, postal address and e-mail address or other information provided by you if you have requested services from us, participated in one of our promotions, or joined our mailing list.

If you are under the age of thirteen (13) years old, you should only submit personal information about yourself with the consent of a parent or guardian.

**USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**

The primary purpose for which we collect personal information is so that we can provide you with our goods and services. Frontier may also use personal information to send you information about its activities, or about goods or services that it believes may be relevant or useful to you.

Examples of how we may use your information include:

a.    to provide certain features or functionality or to improve your user experience, for example by suggesting artists or tours and displaying information about events that are local to you;  
b.    to enable you to access certain features of the Sites;  
c.    for the purposes of conducting promotions;  
d.    for our own statistical and internal business purposes and to improve the Sites;  
e.    for advertising and business promotion purposes, for example to measure the effectiveness of any advertisements displayed on the Sites.

In other respects, we will only use personal information with your consent, or if we are required or permitted by law to do so.  In particular, your information will not be disclosed to any overseas recipients without your prior consent

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a small file which we may store on your computer. We may use cookies to record and hold information to track your internet browser’s behaviour and to enable certain website functions, such as remembering your settings or preferences. Cookies will collect only the necessary information for this purpose.

We use cookies and similar technologies to help us understand how people use the Sites so that we can keep improving your user experience.

We utilise cookies from third parties when you visit our website our use our apps.

You can block cookies on your computer, however this may degrade your user experience on the Sites.  To find out how to see what cookies have been set and how to reject and delete cookies, please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org.

**GOOGLE COOKIES**

Frontier may utilise cookies provided by Google, Inc (“Google”) to help analyse how users use our website. The information generated by these cookies is transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.

Frontier may, from time to time, use the following services provide by Google which utilise cookies. These include Google Analytics, Google Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

To opt-out of analysis by Google Analytics on our website and other websites, please visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout

To opt-out of personalized ad delivery on the Google content network, please visit Google’s Ads Preferences Manager at http://www.google.com/ads/preferences

**EMAIL LISTS**

We may collect your email and, if you provide it, other contact details when you subscribe to our email list, join our membership lists, or enter our promotions. We only use this information for the purpose that we informed you of at the time that you supplied this information.

##  3.    Disclosure

There are limited circumstances where we have to disclose your personal information to third parties, including:

a.    where we are required to by law;  
b.    where we need to in order to fulfill the purpose for which you disclosed the personal information, including but not limited to providing the information to our associated company, Frontier Touring Co. (N.Z) Ltd in New Zealand for the purposes of supplying you with information about our New Zealand tours when you have requested;  
c.    from time to time, to other companies within the Mushroom Group of Companies, or to record companies so that that they can perform certain functions on our behalf. Any personal information transferred between us and our record company in such circumstances will be handled in accordance with the APP’s and this Privacy Policy;  
d.    to third parties to whom we contract out specialised functions (e.g. mailing houses, printing companies and storage servers). If we do disclose personal information to third party contractors under outsourcing or contracting arrangements, we will take steps to ensure that those contractors only use your personal information in order to provide the specific services or to perform the specific functions required by us and store your personal information securely and only for as long as it is necessary to provide the required services or perform the required function; or  
e.    when you authorise us to do so (for example, through your profile settings).

Other than these limited circumstances, we will not disclose your personal information to any third party (including advertisers or other companies) unless you have authorised us to do so.

##  4.    Quality of personal information

We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect from you is accurate, complete and up to date. These include

a.    taking care to accurately collect and store the information you provide to us, and  
b.    where possible, we will run update campaigns to refresh the inform that we collect from you, and  
c.    provide you access to check and the quality of your personal information and promptly correct any personal information that you notify us of as being inaccurate.

##  5.    Storage and security of personal information

We will take reasonable steps to keep any personal information we hold secure from unauthorised disclosure or access, including:

a.    restricting access to authorised personnel only and imposing strict requirements of security and confidentiality on all third parties who store the personal information on our behalf as to how they store and handle personal information.   
b.    regularly assessing the risk of personal information being accessed or disclosed without authorisation and taking all reasonable measures to mitigate those risks.

You agree that in order for us to provide the Website and any incidental goods and services, we may need to store or transfer your personal information to servers located outside of Australia.

##  6.    Accessing and correcting your personal information

We take all reasonable steps to ensure the information it collects from you is accurate, complete and up-to-date. We also takes steps to maintain the security of all personal information provided by you and to prevent misuse or unauthorised access to that information.

Under the Privacy Act (Australian Privacy Principles 12 and 13) you have the right to ask for access to personal information that we hold about you, and ask that we correct that information.

If at any time you wish to access or correct your personal details, please let us know using the contact details below and we will comply with your request. We will ask you to verify your identity before we will disclose the personal information you request or modify that information.

##  7.    Unsubscribe

If at any time you do not wish to be notified about goods, services and promotions offered by us, or if you don’t wish to receive any further communications from us, please contact us by send an email to info@frontiertouring.com.au.

##  8.    How to make a complaint

If you wish to complain to us about how we have handled your personal information you show complain in writing using the details in the ‘How to contact us’ section of this Privacy Policy. We will respond to all complains within 30 days of us receiving your complaint.

##  9.    How to contact us

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, or to make any requests as outlined above, please contact

By mail:  
Frontier Touring  
c/o Business & Legal Affairs  
Dundas Lane, Albert Park, Victoria 3206

By email:  
info@frontiertouring.com.au

##  10.    Policy Changes

We may edit this Privacy Policy from time to time by publishing the changed Privacy Policy on our Sties.  This Privacy Policy was last updated on 15 May 2014.
